SO THE REASON I'M
POINTING IN TODAY
So the reason I'm
pointing in today is
for a criminal
investigation, okay.
So our criminal
investigation is
regarding you, and
some database stuff,
right, ✅
do you have an idea 💡
what this is about?
I think so. Okay.
Well, what do you
think this is about?
I know I've stopped
people to some, you
know, investigation
and kind of looked
like on David, but
then that's it. Okay.
Who do you look 👀 at
David for?
For warrants.
Okay. I mean, I'm not
talking about our long
-coursemate capacity,
right? This goes a
little bit beyond
that. Can you wear
somebody's name?
Yes. ✅ The detective is
asking about a woman
named Madison. She
hadn't reported Lamar
herself. In fact, she
doesn't yet know she's
a victim. Madison was
filming on the set of
Bad Monkey.